<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home for the 21st Century Youth</title>
    <link>https://youthsquad.network/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Home for the 21st Century Youth</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:26:09 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://youthsquad.network/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>50&#43; Indian Entrepreneur Success Stories - rags to riches</title>
      <link>https://youthsquad.network/50-indians-from-rags-to-riches/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:26:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youthsquad.network/50-indians-from-rags-to-riches/</guid>
      <description>With the help of this post, we are sharing you the success stories of Indian entrepreneurs who successfully started with almost nothing.** **
Success Stories of Entrepreneurs which will inspire you.
These stories hopefully will inspire you through your startup journey and will keep you motivated. (these are not in any specific order or based on specific criteria)
Below Mentioned are Indian Entrepreneurs who started with almost nothing in hand and yet were able to make multi-million companies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Becoming A Software Developer</title>
      <link>https://youthsquad.network/software-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:26:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youthsquad.network/software-development/</guid>
      <description>Want to become a Software Developer? Here’s how to get there “How do I become a developer?” — I’ve heard this question a lot, so I decided to write the best guide I can, using only free resources. If you’re an experienced software developer already, feel free to save yourself the time and do something else. Otherwise, read on :).
 “The journey of a thousand miles begins with one step” — Lao Tzu</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of Opportunities To Apply in 2018</title>
      <link>https://youthsquad.network/apply-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:26:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youthsquad.network/apply-2018/</guid>
      <description>Opportunities for Youth ** We&amp;rsquo;ve noted down the best youth opportunities and challenges for June and July 2018. We&amp;rsquo;ve found some fabulous competitions, great events and chances to really make a difference. ** Check the eligibility requirements and deadlines to be sure to you have the best chance of winning!
Attend Social Impact Hack: One Young World &amp;amp; Facebook
Collaborate on innovative solutions to 3 topics in a competitive and inspiring setting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join as A Mentor</title>
      <link>https://youthsquad.network/join-as-a-mentor/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:26:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youthsquad.network/join-as-a-mentor/</guid>
      <description>Name  Email  Describe yourself in few lines   Enter your LinkedIN or any link to let users know more about you       </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to choose which programming language to learn</title>
      <link>https://youthsquad.network/average-salary-software-developer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:26:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youthsquad.network/average-salary-software-developer/</guid>
      <description>Source
Which Programming Language Should I Learn First? Before choosing your first programming language, you should also check out this infographic on What Is Programming And What Do Programmers Do.
So you want to learn programming. Maybe you have asked your developer friends for recommendations and get different answers. They explained with terms that you don&amp;rsquo;t understand (what is object-oriented?!). To help you to pick your first programming language to learn, here is an easy-to-understand infographic that recommends the best option, depending on your purpose and interest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inspiring Lessons From Famous Failures</title>
      <link>https://youthsquad.network/famous-failures/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:26:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youthsquad.network/famous-failures/</guid>
      <description>The names are known, the faces are familiar and their stories are inspirational. However, while we know who they are now, we ignore the failures they went through to get to where they are today. From Oprah Winfrey to Henry Ford, all these greats went through struggles to get to where they are now. Here is looking at the struggles the people who changed the world went through early on in their life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unilever Young Entrepreneurs Awards - €50,000</title>
      <link>https://youthsquad.network/unilever-young-entrepreneurs-awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:26:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youthsquad.network/unilever-young-entrepreneurs-awards/</guid>
      <description>The Unilever Young Entrepreneurs Awards will recognise up to eight winners, including the HRH Prize Winner, in 2018. The eight winners will be selected from a rigorous assessment process led by The University of Cambridge Institute for Sustainability Leadership, culminating in video interviews with our finalist selection panels. All eight winners will be invited to an Accelerator Programme in Cambridge, before making their final pitches in person to a guest judging panel who will decide on the HRH Prize Winner of the 2018 competition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>https://youthsquad.network/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:26:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youthsquad.network/about/</guid>
      <description>Our goal is to  Identifying vulnerable youth through targeted social media campaigns on Facebook Onboarding them on to our Chatbot Platform and provide them the following capbailities  Mentorship and Guidance from successful people from their same community or background  Access to career opportunities and training  Emergency assistance  Platform to share their voice and ideas  &amp;ndash; One of the biggest challenge that we are trying to solve is giving these youth the opportunity to invest their life in something big.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fellowship Opportunities</title>
      <link>https://youthsquad.network/fellowships/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:26:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youthsquad.network/fellowships/</guid>
      <description>Fellowships/Scholarships Back to Top
 Developer Scholarship from Google - Link for Indian students (Others click here). Scholarship Opportunities at Google - Google&amp;rsquo;s scholarship opportunities. Microsoft Scholarship Program - For students at US/Canada/Mexico only. Thiel Fellowship for young innovators - Intended for students under 23yo and offers a total of $100,000 and guidance to drop out of school and pursue other work. The Facebook Fellowship Program - Designed to encourage promising doctoral students who are engaged in areas related to computer science.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Average Salaries Of Software Developer</title>
      <link>https://youthsquad.network/average-salary-software-developer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:26:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youthsquad.network/average-salary-software-developer/</guid>
      <description>https://www.daxx.com/uploads/32746542692_c5b0e810d1_k.jpg
Source
Software Engineer Salaries by Country Apr 20, 2015
The Highest Paying Countries for Software Developers in the World  USA – $92,240 Switzerland – $85,709 Norway – $70,776 Israel – $70,290 Denmark – $70,082 UK – $59,268 Germany – $57,345 Australia – $53,721 Sweden – $53,469 Netherlands – $51,488  This post was updated on February 9, 2018
We&amp;rsquo;ve been publishing our salary overview for three years in a row now.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>